this exercise has given us a string
and we're using element reference to
assign a character of the string
to the variables a b and c
we need to determine what a b and c
reference
so on line two we're referencing the
character at index six of this string
since the strings index is zero based
the character at index six will be the
seventh character
which is the e at the end of welcome
and just to confirm that let's output a
and we see that e
next we're referencing the character at
index 11 of this string
now these spaces are included in the
index count so the character at index 11
of this string is going to be the
uppercase
a of america
and we'll output that as well
finally we're referencing the character
at index 19 of this string
now the string does have 19 characters
but because the index is zero based
the index of the last character in this
string
the exclamation mark is 18. so what
happens when we try to
reference an index that is greater than
the length of this string
let's output it in c
the return value is going to be nil
ruby is not going to throw an error when
you reference an
index that is greater than the length of
a string or an array
instead it will return nil so watch out
for this in your code